I don't get to take a day off because I don't get paid time off.
I have very minimal sick hours and I have to strategically decide when I might,
in a few months, be sick enough to get a day off.
I only get three days for an entire year — so kind of just making it work.
I don't get the same benefits as my permanent staff and I work probably just as hard as they do,
if not more — and I don't get benefits for my children, otherwise it would be at a very high cost.
I don't get any sick time besides my four days.
I don't have any vacation time, so it's a little unfair.
It's almost a two-tier system.
We're almost like, I would say, modern-day serf workers — because the permanent staff are entitled to all the benefits, whereas extra-help staff are not.
Currently our county has 20% of its workforce as extra-help workers.
That's the highest amount of extra-help staff here in the Bay Area.